http://www.catalyst-uk.com/ccs/catalyst-computer-systems/company/privacy-policy

Head OfficeDirections
Catalyst Computer Systems Ltd. Granite House, 58 Loughborough Road, Mountsorrel, Leicestershire,LE12 7AT.
Telephone
+44(0)116 230 1500 (Reduced service)Please email any sales or support queries.
Knowledge Base
Office hours are 9:00am to 5:30pm Monday through Friday (for emergency out of hours support see 'Out of Hours' below).
Out of Hours
See here for details.
Urgent Weekend Hotline:
+44(0)781 804 4086
Emergency Out of Hours:
emergency@catalyst-uk.com
Home
Catalyst Computer Systems
Privacy Policy
An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the web. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. On occasions, we collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to analyse aggregate information, and to audit the use of our site.
Cookies
Catalyst's website and on-line services, may use “cookies”.
Cookies are
files which are sent back and forth with web pages which can be used to identify that you have previously visited a site, or to store small bits of information locally with you. Cookies make web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. The use of cookies is an industry standard - you will find them at most major web sites.
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can block most cookies (except for Flash cookies) by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our sites, or you may experience reduced functionality when accessing certain services. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon you visit our website.
To disable cookies in your browser consult your browsers help system.
Further information about Cookies
Find out more about cookies including how to disable/enable and delete them at the following websites www.aboutcookies.org and www.allaboutcookies.org.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
Data Distribution
Data may be collected from your Platinum DMS for distribution to third parties. We will only do this with your consent by you filling in a Data Permission form giving us permission to transfer your data. Information collected by third parties is governed by their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.
DMS Authorisation, Usage, Diagnostics and Updates
In order to provide monthly rental system updates and for file updates (Parts, PAF etc) our data server will be contacted with your system identification at least once for every day a company data set is accessed. These accesses are recorded and logged securely for service quality purposes.
Catalyst asks customers to help improve Platinum by providing diagnostic and usage information. This information sharing can be enabled or disabled at any point. Please see our Knowledge Base for further details.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our trading policy section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our services.
Web Analytics
This web site uses Piwik, an open-source software for statistical analyses of user accesses. Piwik is privacy-compliant and data is anonymised for storage. Piwik uses "cookies", which are text files stored temporarily on your computer. These files are deleted as soon as your web browser is closed. You can deactivate data recording by Piwik clicking here. If your browser supports "do-not-track" technology and you have turned it on, your visit will be automatically ignored.
The data Piwik collects is never sent to other servers or to third parties; it is used in anonymised form to improve our services. IP addresses are stored in Piwik without the final tuple. We know the network the query came from, not the specific computer.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.
Modifications
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
Modification
This policy was last modified on 8th November 2017.
